Dreyan Enrique Franco Pérez

Valencia, Spain · <u>linkedin.com/in/drevanfranco</u> · +34 633 439 919 · <u>drevanfranco@gmail.com</u> · <u>drevanfranco.vercel.app/</u>

Web developer with experience in ReactJs, NodeJs, MongoDB and TypeScript. I am proficient in developing responsive web applications, using modern frontend frameworks and backend technologies. I have experience in designing and implementing RESTful APIs, working with databases and deploying applications in production environments.

Work Experience

Sharehood Remote

Fullstack Developer

Marzo 2023-Octubre 2023

- Developed and maintained the frontend of a marketplace using React, creating a visually appealing and user-friendly visually appealing and user-friendly interface to enhance the customer shopping experience.
- Participated in the development and maintenance of microservices, ensuring their scalability and efficiency.
- Used Docker and Docker Compose for container creation and management.
- Collaborated with UX/UI using Figma to translate wireframes and mockups into UI designs, using MaterialUI.

ProxyaRemoteFullstack DeveloperFeb 2021–Feb 2022

- Built functionalities for web applications using TypeScript, React, NodeJS and MongoDB.
 - Helped implement GitHub Actions to automate continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) workflows, improving efficiency and consistency in software development and deployment.
 - Performed end-to-end testing to ensure full system functionality from an end-user perspective, ensuring software quality and reliability.
 - Contributed in the design of the REST API that allowed users to manage projects and employees.

Elavon Madrid, Spain

Underwriter and Specialist AML

July 2014–August 2017

- Ensured a thorough and effective verification of Elavon's contractors' documents.
- Verified the agreements signed with contractors and financial evaluation of the documents provided.

EDUCACIÓN

UNIVERSAE Valencia, Spain

Higher Professional Training in Web Applications Development.

SKILLS

- Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Nodejs, MongoDB, Postgres, Playwright and Jest.
- Native in Spanish. C1 in English.